&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：让我们总结一下我们的想法，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So let's summarize our thoughts on,
或者我和你分享的想法，
or my thoughts that I've shared with you,
我想我应该说，它们的各种不同类型的功能。
I guess I should say, on functions of their various different types.
我认为函数声明有一些
It is my opinion that function declarations have some
比他们优越。
superiority to them.
我们甚至还没有谈到所有这些，当我们讲到的时候，我们会回到那些，
We haven't even talked about all of those, we'll come back to those when we get to,
比如浪费，以后。
for example, wasting, later.
但是函数声明比命名函数表达式有一些好处。
But a function declaration has some benefits over a named function expression.
但是命名函数表达式比起
But named function expressions have huge benefits over
匿名函数表达式。
anonymous function expressions.
所以我对后两种感觉比前两种更强烈，
So I feel much more strongly about the second two of these than the first two,
尽管我也倾向于选择命名函数声明。
even though I also do tend to prefer the named function declarations.
所以这只是需要注意的事情，
So it's just something to be aware of,
因为这并不是真正能成为一条硬性规则的东西。
because this isn't really something that can be such a hard and fast rule.
你确实需要看一下各种不同的情况。
You do have to look at the various different cases.
我当然理解为什么人们可能会使用箭头函数
And I certainly understand why people might use an arrow function
当它是五个字符加倍一些变量的时候。
when it's five characters doubling some variable.
但即使在那些你只是想节省一点时间的情况下，
But even in those cases where you're tempted just to save a little bit of time,
我仍然会争辩说这个名字，双倍，
I would still argue that the name, double it,
告诉我一些比看x乘以2更直接的东西。
tells me something more directly than looking at x times 2.
所以我只想让你考虑更大的目标，也就是我们想要
So I just want you to consider that bigger purpose, which is we want to
使我们的代码尽可能有效地进行通信，即使是一目了然，
have our code communicate as effectively as possible, even at a glance,
而不需要有人阅读并在心理上执行一些代码
without somebody having to read and sort of mentally execute some code and
弄清楚它是做什么的，或者考虑它上面的任何类型的拐角情况。
figure out what it does, or consider any sort of corner cases on it.
理想情况下，我们不希望读者不得不做这些事情。
We don't want the reader to have to do those things, ideally.
我们希望他们能够阅读我们的代码
We want them to be able to read our code and
几乎一眼就能明白它的目的。
understand it's purpose almost at a glance.
所以这些就是为什么我更喜欢这种顺序的函数的原因，并且
So those are the reasons why I prefer the functions in this order, and
我会以我的方式向下工作，而且我基本上只会永远
I would work my way down, and I would essentially only ever
在箭头表达式形式中执行匿名函数表达式。
do the anonymous function expression in the arrow expression form.
在那个特殊的情况下，我只会这样做，因为我正在变得词汇化
And in that one particular case, I would only do so because I was getting lexical
点击，我们稍后将在课程中讨论这一点。
clicks, which we'll talk about later in the course.